Finding Aid for the Mae Babitz papers LSC.1740
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 6. Artwork, ca. 1930-1980
  - Street scene with lampposts in brown, green and red, 1955 (Box 31)
    Watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 15" × 19 1/4"
  - Park scene with six people, 1948 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink, pencil and watercolor on paper, 14 1/2" × 19 1/2"
  - Grubbing #3, Los Angeles Scene #22, 1948 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink on paper 14 1/2" × 19 1/2"
  - European buildings with stairways and water fountain, undated (Box 31)
  - Building and parked cars, unfinished, undated (Box 31)
    Pencil and ink on paper, 22 1/2" × 24 1/2" (tears and folds on left side)
  - LA, Vermont and Fifth (Diamond Auto Sale), 1955 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink and pencil on paper, 22 1/4" × 10 1/4"
  - Dr. Blass' Office (Box 31)
    Pencil on paper, 14 3/4" × 20"
  - Jack's Turkish Baths, 1955 (Box 31)
    Crow quill and ink, watercolor and pencil on watercolor paper, 22 1/4" × 12"
  - Two houses and man on porch steps, 1957 (Box 31)
    Pencil and watercolor on illustration board, 22" × 30"
  - Prints of Bradbury Building (Box 32)
    12 items
  - Prints of Watts Towers (Box 32)
    5 items
  - Prints of Bunker Hill, 2nd and Grand (Box 33)
    16 Items